

Min Iles | Software Developer

Professional summary

I am a Software Developer with experience at Dev Academy Bootcamp along with a Bachelor of Fine Arts with Honours from Massey University.

Software Development along with a Fine Arts education has given me an open mind and a passionate curiosity for people, culture, technology, and how different things can work together to create better spaces in our physical world and online.

I have experience working with Youthline and The Peer Tree, two community mental health support organizations. I have been Assistants Director and Photographer on the Board of Meanwhile Gallery for two years. This has developed my ability to adapt to different team environments and collaborate well with others. During my time at Massey University, I covered a variety of papers, including Journalism, Media Studies, Film, Photography, Screen, and Urban Design. I also have a Baristas License for when anyone needs a good cup of coffee.

I am full of curiosity and always open to new points of view and new ways of doing things.

In my free time, I love to meet new people, learn new things, and get out of the city and travel. I have been fortunate enough to spend time overseas in America and Australia for the first half of 2020.

I am excited to bring my diverse skill set and experience to new challenges and new communities, learning all the more from where I end up.

Experience:

Dev Academy - Software Developer Student

Online

03/2023 - 07/2023

- Experience working in teams and pair programming from 9 5
- Human skills development and reflections around collaboration.

MEANWHILE Gallery - Assistants Director | Photographer | On the board

Wellington

01/2022 - Current

• Managing gallery assistants, and coordinating Gallery sitters during exhibitions.

- ➤ Min.elliot48@gmail.com
- Wellington, New Zealand
- https://github.com/Tominne
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/minin iles-79bb2a221/

Skills

- Javascript | Typescript
- HTML coding
- SQL Database Management
- OpenAPI
- React
- Collaboration
- Photography | Film
- Community Engagement
- Research | Writing

Education

03/2023 - 07/2023

Dev Academy

Wellington

Software Development

01/2019 - 11/2024

Massey University

Wellington

Bachelor of Fine Arts: Fine Arts and

Creative Cultures - Honours

Samuel Marsden Collegiate College

Wellington

- Taking photography of exhibitions, editing, and sharing material on social media.
- Getting people involved with the gallery and exhibiting their own art in the space.

Kites | **The Peer Tree** - **Social Media Manager** | **Group Facilitator** Wellington

10/2020 - 01/2023

- Generating social media strategies and frameworks.
- Produced photo and video content with digital editing skills.
- Scheduling social media posts to maximize engagement.
- Connecting with members of the community to create personal genuine content to show off what a cool resource The Peer tree is.

Te Horo Forestry - Environmental Work

Te Horo, New Zealand 09/2022 - 12/2023

- Planting thousands of native trees and tree protection at the Te Horo Forest land.
- Manage workers and volunteers.
- Ensure everyone's safety and well-being,

YOUTHLINE - Learning Facilitator

Wellington

02/2021 - 09/2021

- Created a safe relaxed environment for a variety of young people from all walks of life mixed with learning and community.
- Helped students to develop self-confidence around individual skills and leadership potential.
- Assisted with fun activities or workbook tasks and adapting each to individuals needs.